A Guide to the Rockefeller foundation records, projects, SG 1.16-1.19 (A90-A93) FA469
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A91), 1979-1989; 1.17; 96.19 Cubic Feet; 217 letter size document storage boxes (Boxes 1-217) 1 half legal size document storage box (Box 7A) and 1 legal size document storage box (Box 218)
  - United States, 200
    - United States - Population Studies, 200P
      - University of Michigan - Fertility Decline in Thailand, 1983-1987 (Box 30, Folder 171)
      - University of Michigan - Fertility Decline in Thailand: Supplementary Material (Box 30, Folder 172)
      - University of Washington - Mammalian Fertilization, 1979-1981, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 173)
      - Yale University - Hormonal Contraceptives, 1981-1986 (Box 30, Folder 174, Box 31, Folder 175)
      - Yale University - Hormonal Contraceptives: Supplementary Material (Box 31, Folder 176-177)
      - Yale University - Rhesus Monkey Research, 1980-1981, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 178)
    - United States - Humanities and Arts, 200R
      - American Association of Museums - Museums and Education, 1984-1987, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 179)
      - Boston Critic, Inc. - New Boston Review Supplement, 1982-1987 (Box 31, Folder 180)
      - Boston Critic, Inc. - New Boston Review Supplement: Supplementary Material (Box 32, Folder 181-185, Box 33, Folder 186-189)
      - Columbia University - Council for European Studies, 1977-1985 (Box 33, Folder 190, Box 34, Folder 191-192)
        Grant in support of translation costs for a volume of essays on "The New Family and the New Woman, 1914-1945"
      - ETV Endowment of South Carolina, Inc. - International TV Revue, 1984-1987 (Box 34, Folder 193)
      - Global Village - Documentary Film, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 194)
      - Louisiana State University - Eighteenth-Century Short-Title Catalogue for North America, 1982-1987, 1989-1990 (Box 34, Folder 195-196, Box 35, Folder 197-198)
      - Middlebury College - Rural English Teaching, 1976-1990 (Box 35, Folder 199-202, Box 36, Folder 203-205)
      - National Archives Trust Fund Board - Women's History, 1981-1982, 1984-1986, 1988-1990, 1993-1996, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 206)
      - National Archives Trust Fund Board - Women's History: Supplementary Material (Box 36, Folder 207)
      - National Council on Foreign Language and International Studies, 1982-1983, 1985-1986, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 208, Box 37, Folder 209-211)
      - National Guild of Community Schools of the Arts - Young Composer Awards, 1983-1987, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 212-213)
      - Queens College, New York - Urban Folklore, 1984-1985 (Box 37, Folder 214)
        Grant rescinded
      - Smithsonian Institution - Humanities Fellowships, 1975-1985, 1987-1988, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 215-218)
        For use by its Woodrow Wilson International Center for Scholars
      - Smithsonian Institution - Humanities Fellowships: Supplementary Material (Box 38, Folder 219-221)
      - University of Massachusetts - Urban Humanities Writing, 1983-1988 (Box 39, Folder 222)
      - University of North Carolina - Journalists Fellowships, 1980-1987 (Box 39, Folder 223-224)
      - University of North Carolina - Journalists Fellowships: Supplementary Material (Box 39, Folder 225)
      - University of North Carolina -Women's Studies Institute for Teachers, 1982-1988 (Box 39, Folder 226-227, Box 40, Folder 228)
      - University of North Carolina -Women's Studies Institute for Teachers: Supplementary Material (Box 40, Folder 229-232)
      - Yale University - Teachers Institute, Dissemination, 1983-1988, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 233-238, Box 42, Folder 239-240)
    - United States - Social Sciences, 200S
      - Overseas Development Council, 1968-1985, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 241-244, Box 43, Folder 245-250, Box 44, Folder 251-255, Box 45, Folder 256-260, Box 46, Folder 261)
      - Overseas Development Council: Supplementary Materials (Box 46, Folder 262-264, Box 47, Folder 265-268, Box 48, Folder 269-273, Box 49, Folder 274)
    - United States - Virus Studies, 200V
      - Yale University - Reference System, 1982-1986, 1988 (Box 49, Folder 275)
  - Equal Opportunity Projects in Southern United States, 275
    - Save the Children Federation - Community Development, 1975-1986 (Box 49, Folder 276-278, Box 50, Folder 279-280)
    - Save the Children Federation - Community Development: Supplementary Material (Box 50, Folder 281)
  - Equal Opportunity Projects, 277
    - Jobs for America's Graduates, Inc., 1980-1990 (Box 50, Folder 282-284, Box 51, Folder 285-290, Box 52, Folder 291-295, Box 53, Folder 296-298)
    - Jobs for America's Graduates, Inc.: Supplementary Material (Box 53, Folder 299-302, Box 54, Folder 303-307, Box 55, Folder 308-309)
  - Prizes for Non-Academically-Affiliated Scholars, 287
    - Prizes for Non-Academically-Affiliated Scholars, 1982-1986, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 310)
    - American Historical Association, 1982-1984, 1986-1990, 1992 (Box 55, Folder 311)
    - American Philosophical Association, 1982-1987, 1990, 1992-1993 (Box 55, Folder 312)
    - Modern Language Association, 1982-1988, 1990-1992 (Box 55, Folder 313)
  - Congressional Fellows Program, 288
    - Congressional Fellows Program, 1982-1983, 1986-1987 (Box 55, Folder 314)
    - American Historical Association, 1982-1985, 1987 (Box 56, Folder 315)
  - Vectors of Disease Agents, 299
    Purpose: Toward a research on arthropod transmission of parasitic diseases of plants and animals
    - Vectors of Disease Agents, 1980-1985 (Box 56, Folder 316)
    - Cornell University - Arthropod Transmission, 1980-1985 (Box 56, Folder 318)
    - Harvard University - Arthropod Transmission, 1980-1986 (Box 56, Folder 319-321)
    - Michigan State University - Arthropod Transmission, 1982-1985 (Box 57, Folder 322)
    - Pennsylvania State University - Arthropod Transmission, 1983-1987 (Box 57, Folder 323)
    - University of California, Berkeley - Arthropod Transmission, 1980-1985, 1987 (Box 57, Folder 324-327)
  - Argentina, 301
    - Argentina - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 301E
      - Roldan S., Eduardo R., 1984-1986 (Box 58, Folder 328-330)
      - Roldan S., Eduardo R., 1984-1986 (Box 58, Folder 328A)
      - Staneloni, Roberto J., 1984-1987 (Box 58, Folder 331)
      - Staneloni, Roberto J., 1984-1987 (Box 58, Folder 331A)
    - Argentina - Population Studies, 301P
      - Burgos, Mario H., 1980-1981, 1992 (Box 58, Folder 332)
      - Universidad Nacional de Cuyo - Gossypol Effect on Flagellate Cells, 1982-1986 (Box 58, Folder 333)
        Principal investigator - Mario H. Burgos
  - Brazil, 305
    - Hospital Santa Casa de Misericórdia - LaGuardia, Katherine D., 1987-1989 (Box 58, Folder 334)
    - Hospital Santa Casa de Misericórdia - LaGuardia, Katherine D., 1987-1989 (Box 58, Folder 334A)
    - Universidade Federal de Minas Gerais - Vosti, Stephen A., 1983-1988, 1990 (Box 59, Folder 335-337)
    - Universidade Federal de Minas Gerais - Vosti, Stephen A., 1983-1988, 1990 (Box 59, Folder 335A)
    - Brazil - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 305E
      - Aragón V., Luis E., 1984-1987 (Box 59, Folder 338-340, Box 60, Folder 341-342)
      - Aragón V., Luis E., 1984-1987 (Box 59, Folder 338A)
      - Borges de Oliveira, Celso L., 1982-1984 (Box 60, Folder 343)
      - Borges de Oliveira, Celso L., 1982-1984 (Box 60, Folder 343A)
      - Dahab, Sonia, 1976-1986 (Box 60, Folder 344)
      - Dehab, Sonia, 1976-1986 (Box 60, Folder 344A)
      - Fernandez, José Carrera, 1981-1987 (Box 60, Folder 345-346)
      - Fernandez, José Carrera, 1981-1987 (Box 60, Folder 345A)
      - Gentil Marques, Carlos Alberto, 1982-1988 (Box 61, Folder 347)
      - Gentil Marques, Carlos Alberto, 1982-1988 (Box 61, Folder 347A)
      - Gonzaga S., Jorge Antonio, 1982-1987 (Box 61, Folder 348)
      - Gonzaga S., Jorge Antonio, 1982-1987 (Box 61, Folder 348A)
      - Guimarães, Antonio Sergio Alfredo., 1979-1988 (Box 61, Folder 349)
      - Guimarães, Antonio Sergio Alfredo, 1979-1988 (Box 61, Folder 349A)
      - Soares, Carlos Alberto Caroso, 1980-1988 (Box 61, Folder 350, Box 62, Folder 351)
      - Soares, Carlos Alberto Caroso, 1980-1988 (Box 61, Folder 350A)
      - do Vale, Maria do Carmo Fonseca, 1984-1988 (Box 62, Folder 352)
      - do Vale, Maria do Carmo Fonseca, 1984-1988 (Box 62, Folder 352A)
    - Brazil - Population Studies, 305P
      - Brazilian Center for Analysis and Planning (CEBRAP) - Fertility, 1982-1986 (Box 62, Folder 353-355)
        CEBRAP - Centro Brasileiro de Análise e Planejamento
      - Federal University of Bahia - Hormonal Regulation of Prostaglandin Synthesis, 1984-1985, 1987-1988 (Box 62, Folder 356)
        Universidade Federal da Bahia
    - Brazil - Agricultural Development, 305UD
      - Federal University of Bahia - Agricultural Programs, 1979-1984 (Box 62, Folder 357, Box 63, Folder 358)
      - Federal University of Bahia - Agricultural Programs: Supplementary Material (Box 63, Folder 359-362)
      - Federal University of Bahia - Integrated Rural Development, 1982-1984 (Box 63, Folder 363)
  - Chile, 309
    - Center for Development Studies (CED) - Economic Order and Democracy, 1983-1986 (Box 63, Folder 364)
      Centro de Estudios del Desarrollo
    - Center for Development Studies (CED) - Economic order and Democracy: Supplementary Material (Box 64, Folder 365-367)
    - Chile - Population Studies, 309P
      - University of Chile - Endocrine Control, 1980-1984 (Box 64, Folder 368-369)
  - Colombia, 311
    - Fundacion para la Aplicacion y Enseñanza de las Ciencias (FUNDAEC) - Rural Development, 1979-1982, 1984-1986 (Box 64, Folder 370-371, Box 65, Folder 372-374)
    - Fundacion para la Aplicacion y Enseñanza de las Ciencias (FUNDAEC) - Textbooks, 1980, 1982-1986 (Box 65, Folder 375)
    - Fundacion para la Aplicacion y Enseñanza de las Ciencias (FUNDAEC) - Textbooks: Supplementary Material (Box 65, Folder 376-377, Box 66, Folder 378)
    - Universidad del Valle - Fundación para la Educación Superior (FES), 1964-1965 (Box 66, Folder 379-380)
    - Universidad del Valle - Fundación para la Educación Superior (FES) - Tax Status, 1966-1976, 1980, 1983 (Box 66, Folder 381)
    - Colombia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 311E
      - Ayarza M., Miguel Angel, 1979-1988 (Box 66, Folder 382, Box 67, Folder 383)
      - Ayarza M., Miguel Angel, 1979-1988 (Box 67, Folder 382A)
    - Colombia - Population studies, 311P
      - Determinants of Fertility Change in Colombia, 1981-1986 (Box 67, Folder 384)
  - Mexico, 323
    - El Colegio de Mexico - Christenson, Bruce A., 1985-1989 (Box 67, Folder 385-386)
    - El Colegio de Mexico - Christenson, Bruce A., 1985-1989 (Box 67, Folder 385A)
    - Mexico - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 323D
      - National School of Agriculture, Graduate School - Rural Development, 1972-1984 (Box 67, Folder 387, Box 68, Folder 388-393, Box 69, Folder 394-395)
        Institucion de Enseñanza e Investigacion en Ciencias Agricolas, Colegio de Postgraduados, Chapingo, México
      - National School of Agriculture, Graduate School - Rural Development: Supplementary Material (Box 69, Folder 396-398, Box 70, Folder 399-403)
  - England, 401
    - England - Medical Sciences, 401A
      - Imperial College of Science and Technology - Parasite Epidemiology, 1983-1988 (Box 71, Folder 404)
      - Imperial College of Science and Technology - Parasite Epidemiology: Supplementary Material (Box 71, Folder 405-406)
      - University of Bristol - Reproductive Immunology, 1970-1982 (Box 71, Folder 407-408)
      - University of Bristol - Reproductive Immunology: Supplementary Material (Box 71, Folder 409)
    - England - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 401D
      - Commonwealth Agricultural Bureaux - Africa Agricultural Conference, 1983-1984 (Box 72, Folder 410)
      - Commonwealth Agricultural Bureaux - Africa Agricultural Conference: Supplementary Material (Box 72, Folder 411)
      - Institute of Development Studies - Rural Development Publications, 1984-1989 (Box 72, Folder 412-413)
      - Plant Breeding Institute - Genetics, 1982-1988 (Box 72, Folder 414, Box 73, Folder 415-417)
      - Plant Breeding Institute - Genetics: Supplementary Materials (Box 73, Folder 418)
  - Canada, 427
    - Canada - Medical Sciences, 427A
      - University of Toronto - Clinical Epidemiology, 1984-1987 (Box 73, Folder 419)
  - Windward Islands, 455
    - Windward Islands - Schistosomiasis, 455W
      - St. Lucia - Conference - Schistosomiasis, 1979-1987 (Box 73, Folder 420-421, Box 74, Folder 422-425)
      - St. Lucia - Conference - Schistosomiasis, 1979-1987 (Box 73, Folder 420A)
  - India, 464
    - India - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 464E
      - Agarwal, Ashok, 1983-1986, 1988 (Box 74, Folder 426)
      - Agarwal, Ashok, 1983-1986, 1988 (Box 74, Folder 426A)
      - Kashyap, Lallan Ram, 1982-1985 (Box 75, Folder 427)
      - Kashyap, Lallan Ram, 1982-1985 (Box 75, Folder 427A)
      - Sahni, Mukesh Kumar, 1984-1988 (Box 75, Folder 428)
      - Sahni, Mukesh Kumar, 1984-1988 (Box 75, Folder 428A)
      - Singh, Aqbal, 1982-1984 (Box 75, Folder 429)
      - Singh, Aqbal, 1982-1984 (Box 75, Folder 429A)
  - Bangladesh, 466
    - Bangladesh - Medical Sciences, 466A
      - Kabir, Iqbal, 1984-1986 (Box 75, Folder 430)
    - Bangladesh - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 466E
      - Khandker, Shahidur Rahman, 1983-1987 (Box 75, Folder 431)
      - Khandker, Shahidur Rahman, 1983-1987 (Box 75, Folder 431A)
  - China, 601
    - China - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 601D
      - Academia Sinica - Genetic Manipulation Conference, 1984-1986 (Box 78, Folder 452)
    - China - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 601E
      - Cao, Jun, 1981-1989 (Box 78, Folder 453)
      - Cao, Jun, 1981-1989 (Box 78, Folder 453A)
      - Jin, Ji-yun, 1981-1986 (Box 78, Folder 454)
      - Jin, Ji-yun, 1981-1986 (Box 78, Folder 454A)
      - Kang, Yu-lin, 1982-1988 (Box 79, Folder 455)
      - Kang, Yu-lin, 1982-1988 (Box 79, Folder 455A)
      - Li, You-lan, 1982-1988 (Box 79, Folder 456)
      - Li, You-lan, 1982-1988 (Box 79, Folder 456A)
      - Liu, Yi-xun, 1983-1987 (Box 79, Folder 457-458)
      - Liu, Yi-xun, 1983-1987 (Box 79, Folder 457A)
      - Ma, Rong, 1984-1989 (Box 79, Folder 459)
      - Ma, Rong, 1984-1989 (Box 79, Folder 459A)
      - Wang, Kan, 1984-1988, 1990 (Box 79, Folder 460)
      - Wang, Kan, 1984-1988, 1990 (Box 79, Folder 460A)
      - Wang, Ren, 1981-1986, 1999 (Box 80, Folder 461)
      - Wang, Ren, 1981-1986, 1999 (Box 80, Folder 461A)
      - Wang, Shao-ke, 1982-1989 (Box 80, Folder 462)
      - Wang, Shao-ke, 1982-1989 (Box 80, Folder 462A)
      - Wang, Shu-zhen, 1981-1987, 1990 (Box 80, Folder 463)
      - Wang, Shu-zhen, 1981-1987, 1990 (Box 80, Folder 463A)
      - Yang, Hong, 1981-1985 (Box 80, Folder 464)
      - Yang, Hong, 1981-1985 (Box 80, Folder 464A)
      - Zhao, Zhifan, 1982-1989 (Box 80, Folder 465)
      - Zhao, Zhifan, 1982-1989 (Box 80, Folder 465A)
    - China - Population Studies, 601P
      - Beijing University - Reproductive Biology, 1979-1980, 1986 (Box 80, Folder 466)
      - Chinese Academy of Medical Sciences - Gossypol Pharmacokinetics, 1984-1988 (Box 80, Folder 467)
      - Chinese Academy of Sciences - Reproductive Endocrinology, 1979-1980 (Box 81, Folder 468)
  - Taiwan, 605
    - Asian Vegetable Research and Development Center - Goldman, Abraham, 1984 (Box 81, Folder 469)
  - Japan, 609
    - Japan - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 609E
      - Endo, Yoshihiro, 1984-1987 (Box 81, Folder 470)
      - Endo, Yoshihiro, 1984-1987 (Box 81, Folder 470A)
      - Hosoi, Yoshihiko, 1984-1986 (Box 81, Folder 471)
      - Hosoi, Yoshihiko, 1984-1986 (Box 81, Folder 471A)
  - Korea, 613
    - Korea - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 613E
      - Kim, Hwa Yeong, 1984-1988 (Box 81, Folder 472)
      - Kim, Hwa Yeong, 1984-1988 (Box 81, Folder 472A)
  - Thailand, 617
    - Mahidol University - Salaya Campus Evaluation, 1984-1985 (Box 81, Folder 473)
    - Thailand - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 617E
      - Toowicharanont, Prapaporn, 1983-1986 (Box 81, Folder 474)
      - Toowicharanont, Prapaporn, 1983-1986 (Box 81, Folder 474A)
      - Jampates, Rachanee, 1978-1985, 1988 (Box 81, Folder 475)
      - Jampates, Rachanee, 1978-1985, 1988 (Box 81, Folder 475A)
      - Isvilanonda, Somporn, 1979-1989 (Box 82, Folder 476)
      - Isvilanonda, Somporn, 1979-1989 (Box 82, Folder 476A)
      - Tumwasorn, Sornthep, 1982-1987, 1991 (Box 82, Folder 477)
      - Tumwasorn, Sornthep, 1982-1987, 1991 (Box 82, Folder 477A)
      - Deetae, Suchint, 1979-1988 (Box 82, Folder 478)
      - Deetae, Suchint, 1979-1988 (Box 82, Folder 478A)
      - Luxsanakoses, Sunchai, 1979-1986 (Box 82, Folder 479)
      - Luxsanakoses, Sunchai, 1979-1986 (Box 82, Folder 479A)
      - Kachonpadunkitti, Yongyout, 1983-1987 (Box 83, Folder 480)
      - Kachonpadunkitti, Yongyout, 1983-1987 (Box 83, Folder 480A)
    - Thailand - Population Studies, 617P
      - Khon Kaen University - Rural-Urban Migration, 1982-1986, 1990 (Box 83, Folder 481)
      - Mahidol University - Biosynthesis of hCG (Human Chorionic Gonadotropin), 1980-1983 (Box 83, Folder 482)
      - Mahidol University - Thailand Fertility Decline, 1983-1985, 1987-1988 (Box 83, Folder 483)
  - International Center for Living Aquatic Resources Management (ICLARM), 626
    - International Center for Living Aquatic Resources Management (ICLARM) - Minutes (Box 83, Folder 484)
    - International Center for Living Aquatic Resources Management (ICLARM), 1987-1989 (Box 83, Folder 485)
    - International Center for Living Aquatic Resources Management (ICLARM), 1984-1986 (Box 83, Folder 486)
    - International Center for Living Aquatic Resources Management (ICLARM), 1983 (Box 84, Folder 487)
    - International Center for Living Aquatic Resources Management (ICLARM), 1982 (Box 84, Folder 488-490)
    - International Center for Living Aquatic Resources Management (ICLARM), 1981 (Box 84, Folder 491)
    - International Center for Living Aquatic Resources Management (ICLARM), 1980 (Box 85, Folder 492)
    - International Center for Living Aquatic Resources Management (ICLARM), 1979 (Box 85, Folder 493-494)
    - International Center for Living Aquatic Resources Management (ICLARM), 1978 (Box 85, Folder 495)
    - International Center for Living Aquatic Resources Management (ICLARM), 1977 (Box 85, Folder 496)
    - International Center for Living Aquatic Resources Management (ICLARM), 1976 (Box 86, Folder 497)
    - International Center for Living Aquatic Resources Management (ICLARM), 1975 (Box 86, Folder 498-499)
    - International Center for Living Aquatic Resources Management (ICLARM), 1974 (Box 86, Folder 500-501, Box 87, Folder 502)
    - International Center for Living Aquatic Resources Management (ICLARM), 1973 (Box 87, Folder 503-504)
    - International Center for Living Aquatic Resources Management (ICLARM), 1972 (Box 87, Folder 505)
    - International Center for Living Aquatic Resources Management (ICLARM): Supplementary Material (Box 87, Folder 506-507, Box 88, Folder 508-512, Box 89, Folder 513-514)
    - International Center for Living Aquatic Resources Management (ICLARM) - Brakke, David F., 1978 (Box 89, Folder 515)
      Award rescinded
    - International Center for Living Aquatic Resources Management (ICLARM) - Brakke, David F., 1978 (Box 89, Folder 515A)
    - International Center for Living Aquatic Resources Management (ICLARM) - Colman, John A., 1982-1986 (Box 89, Folder 516)
    - International Center for Living Aquatic Resources Management (ICLARM) - Colman, John A., 1982-1986 (Box 89, Folder 516A)
    - International Center for Living Aquatic Resources Management (ICLARM) - Personnel, 1974-1976 (Box 89, Folder 517)
  - Indonesia, 652
    - Gadjah Mada University - Burch, Carol-Carmen, 1981-1985 (Box 89, Folder 518)
    - Gadjah Mada University - Burch, Carol-Carmen, 1981-1985 (Box 89, Folder 518A)
    - University of Indonesia - Molyneaux, John W., 1984-1989, 1991 (Box 90, Folder 519-520)
    - University of Indonesia - Molyneaux, John W., 1984-1989, 1991 (Box 90, Folder 519A)
    - Indonesia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 652E
      - Hakimi, Mohammad, 1982-1988 (Box 90, Folder 521)
      - Hakimi, Mohammad, 1982-1988 (Box 90, Folder 521A)
      - Kamiso, Handoyo N., 1980-1986 (Box 90, Folder 522)
      - Kamiso, Handoyo N., 1980-1986 (Box 90, Folder 522A)
      - Lelana, Iwan Yusuf Bambang, 1978-1987 (Box 90, Folder 523)
      - Lelana, Iwan Yusuf Bambang, 1978-1987 (Box 90, Folder 523A)
      - Makmuri, Muchlas, 1981-1987 (Box 91, Folder 524)
      - Makmuri, Muchlas, 1981-1987 (Box 91, Folder 524A)
      - Mangkusubroto, Guritno, 1979-1986 (Box 91, Folder 525)
      - Mangkusubroto, Guritno, 1979-1986 (Box 91, Folder 525A)
      - Wirosoebroto, Retno Widaningroem, 1982-1986 (Box 91, Folder 526)
      - Wirosoebroto, Retno Widaningroem, 1982-1986 (Box 91, Folder 526A)
      - Riswandha Imawan, 1982-1989 (Box 91, Folder 527)
      - Riswandha Imawan, 1982-1989 (Box 91, Folder 527A)
      - Sabarnurdin, Mohammad Sambas, 1982-1988 (Box 91, Folder 528)
      - Sabarnurdin, Mohammad Sambas, 1982-1988 (Box 91, Folder 528A)
      - Sadjimin, Tonny, 1981-1986 (Box 92, Folder 529)
        Second fellowship
      - Sadjimin, Tonny, 1981-1986 (Box 92, Folder 529A)
      - Sairin, Sjafri, 1981-1987 (Box 92, Folder 530)
      - Sairin, Sjafri, 1981-1987 (Box 92, Folder 530A)
      - Tjokrosonto, Soesanto, 1981-1988 (Box 92, Folder 531)
      - Tjokrosonto, Soesanto, 1981-1988 (Box 92, Folder 531A)
      - Suparmo, 1980-1988 (Box 92, Folder 532)
      - Suparmo, 1980-1988 (Box 92, Folder 532A)
      - Wasito, 1981-1987 (Box 93, Folder 533)
      - Wasito, 1981-1987 (Box 93, Folder 533A)
      - Wibowo M., Ali, 1982-1987 (Box 93, Folder 534)
      - Wibowo M., Ali, 1982-1987 (Box 93, Folder 534A)
    - Indonesia - Population Studies, 652P
      - Yayasan Kusuma Buana, 1982-1984 (Box 93, Folder 535)
        Kusuma Buana Foundation
    - Indonesia - Agricultural Development, 652UD
      - Gadjah Mada University - Staff Development, 1972-1984, 1986-1987 (Box 93, Folder 536)
      - Gadjah Mada University - Winged Beans, 1977-1981, 1983 (Box 93, Folder 537)
      - Gadjah Mada University - Winged Beans: Supplementary Material (Box 94, Folder 538)
  - Norway, 767
    - Norway - Medical Sciences, 767A
      - University of Oslo - Regulation of Testicular Function, 1979-1984, 1986-1987 (Box 94, Folder 539)
  - Poland, 789
    - Poland - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 789D
      - Agriculture, 1981-1983, 1985-1987, 1989 (Box 94, Folder 540-542, Box 95, Folder 543-546)
      - Agriculture: Supplementary Material (Box 95, Folder 547, Box 96, Folder 548-551)
      - Agriculture - Conference, 1982-1988 (Box 96, Folder 552, Box 97, Folder 553-557, Box 98, Folder 558-559)
  - Turkey, 805
    - Turkey - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 805E
      - Cakmak, Erol Hasan, 1981-1987 (Box 98, Folder 560)
      - Cakmak, Erol Hasan, 1981-1987 (Box 98, Folder 560A)
      - Cakmak, Erol Hasan: Supplementary Material (Box 98, Folder 561)
  - Egypt, 812
    - Egypt - Medical Sciences, 812A
      - Osman, Gamal S., 1983-1987, 1989 (Box 99, Folder 562)
    - Egypt - Population Studies, 812P
      - Al Azhar University - Data Analysis of Contraceptive Implants, 1981-1985, 1989 (Box 99, Folder 563)
      - Contraceptive Implants, 1979-1987 (Box 99, Folder 564-565)
  - Israel, 825
    - Israel - Medical Sciences, 825A
      - Weizmann Institute of Science - Fertility Regulation, 1978-1989 (Box 99, Folder 566-567, Box 100, Folder 568-569)
      - Weizmann Institute of Science - Fertility Regulation: Supplementary Material (Box 100, Folder 570-572)
    - Israel - Population Studies, 825P